<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="no_help_available">
      There is no help available at this time.
    </string>
    <string name="about_help_topics">
      Help is available for each section of this app.
    </string>

    <string name="help_page_intro">Click on one of the icons below to learn the rules for playing the game!</string>
    <string name="help_page_intro_html">
    <![CDATA[
      For information on the different parts of this app, touch one of the images below:
       ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="help_title_section1">Mexican Train Dominoes</string>
    <string name="help_text_section1">
     Mexican Train Dominoes
    </string>
    <string name="topic_section1">
    <![CDATA[
         <p>
       GENERAL:
            Domino games begin by shuffling the pieces that have been turned face down so the
            "spots" do not show. Players then draw the required number of pieces. For 2,3 or 4
            players, draw 15 dominoes each; for 5 or 6 players draw 12 each; and for 7 or 8 players
            draw 11 each.
        </p>
      <p>
        OBJECTIVE:
            To play off all your dominoes. You play off onto your own train, onto the Mexican·Train
            and onto other players\' marked trains.
       </p>
      <p>
        FIRST PLAYER:
            Open the Mexican Train station by placing your highest double in the center. You may then
            begin your train on one of the eight "sidings" of the station by playing off a domino
            matching the station number. Your train should "depart" the station heading towards you.
       </p>
      <p>
            When the first player has no double, the next player opens the station. If no one has a
            double, draw in turn until one is found
        </p>
      <p>
            Continue to play off on your own train until you have no more matches.
            Any left over tiles are called "empties". These may be played later on the Mexican Train when
            new sidings are started that all players may use. (When all eight directions from the station
            have been taken, start new sidings off to the side and out of the way.)
        </p>
      <p>
        SUBSEQUENT PLAY:
            Play always rotates to the left. At your turn, play on your own traIn, on the Mexican Train,
            or on other players\' marked train. You can play off a series of dominoes only on the
            turn when you start your train. After your train "has departed" the station, play only
            one domino per turn, unless you play a double (see below) If you have a choice of plays,
            make any.
        </p>
      <p>
            Whenever you have no play, draw once from the bone  yard. If you still have no play, place
            a marker (a button or a penny works) on the last tile of your train, if you\'ve begun it.
            You may remove your marker by playing on your train later. As long as your train has a
            marker, you may not play on your train, but any other player can. However, you can play
            elsewhere.
        </p>
      <p>
        PLAYING DOUBLES:/n
            When you play a double you must make another play on that double if you can. If you can\'t,
            draw one domino from the bone yard. If you can play it, that\'s fine. If not. place a marker
            on your·train (if it does not already have one) and your turn is over. In this case, the
            next player must play on the double, and if unable must also draw once from the bone yard.
            1f the double still cannot be matched, that player\'s train also gets a marker. This action
            continues until someone plays off the double: players already with a marker can play
            their drawn tile only to satisfy the double.
        </p>
      <p>
        EXCEPTIONS TO DOUBLES REQUIREMENTS:/n
            1) The double to play on is the last domino of its number
            2) You play a double to remove the marker from your own train, with no requirement that
               you or the next players satisfy that double
            3) If the double is your last domino, ending the game immediately.
        </p>
      <p>
        SCORING:
            As soon as one player is out of dominoes, all play stops and players report the sum of
            their remaining dominoes to the scorekeeper. After an agreed number of rounds, whoever
            has the lowest score is the winner. (Note: begin each round with a new player, rotating
            to the left.)
        </p>
      ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="help_title_section2">Scrabble</string>
    <string name="help_text_section2">
     Scrabble
    </string>
    <string name="topic_section2">
    <![CDATA[
      <p>
        There are no rules available for this game at this time
        </p>
       ]]>
    </string>

</resources>












